Guide to the Sylvester Manor Archive 1649-1996 MSS.208
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Record Group VI: Photographic Material
  - Series B: Sylvester Manor, 27 Craigie Street
    - Mounted Photographs: Cabinets Cards, Picture Postcard of Manor Houses - Pelham, Phillipse, Sagtikos, St. George Barbados, circa 1900 - 1948; cuid5558 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Photograph: Congregational Church, Old Lyme, CT, 1924 May; cuid5559 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Photographs: Unidentified Manor Grounds, Priest, undated, circa 1940s; cuid5560 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Photographs: "Calf Christening at Sylvester," Esther B. Fiske, Unidentified Children, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5561 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Photograph: Portrait of "Empress Russia", undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5562 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Photographs with Notation, Reproductions: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Unidentified People, circa 1895; 1975 Summer; cuid5563 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Unidentified Man, undated, circa 1880 - 1960s; cuid5564 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Mounted Photographs: Lenox, MA, Unidentified Couples & Landscapes, undated, circa 1889; cuid5565 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Gardens, Unidentified Man, Woman, Child, 1924; undated, circa 1920 - 1960s; cuid5566 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Photographs with Envelope: Horsfords in Sylvester Manor Garden, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5567 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Photographs: Williamsburg, VA & Unidentified Buildings, undated, circa 1920 - 1960s; cuid5568 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Gardens, Unidentified Groups, Woman & Dog, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5569 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Photograph: Steamship Kelpie, Unidentified Passengers, undated, circa 1915; cuid5570 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Mounted Photograph: Sylvester Manor Garden, Unidentified Wedding Party, undated, circa 1940s; cuid5571 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Gardens, Unidentified Woman, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5572 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Knot Garden, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5573 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Mounted Photographs, Picture Postcard: Sylvester Manor Gardens, Hand-tinted Image, Unidentified Groups, Women, Children, undated, circa 1880 - 1940s; cuid5574 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Photograph: Sylvester Manor Garden, Grape Arbor, undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5575 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Mounted Photographs: Industrial & Maritime Images by Dame, Stoddard & Kendall, undated, circa 1890s; cuid5576 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Photographs with Envelope: Old Lyme, CT & Unidentified Grounds, Gardens, undated, circa 1915 - 1924; cuid5577 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Mounted Photograph: Gardiners Island Interior, Unidentified Woman, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5578 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: Boston & Cambridge, MA Grounds, Gardens & Unidentified Homes, Woman, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5579 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Photograph: Craigie Street Grounds, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5580 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Mounted Photograph: Unidentified Interior, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5581 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Interior, undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5582 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Unidentified Men & Woman, Cow, Peacocks, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5583 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Mounted Photographs: Roswell Ward Library, undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5584 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Interiors, Unidentified Men, Women, Peacocks, undated, circa 1923; cuid5585 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Photographs with Envelope: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Interiors, Unidentified Men, Women, Peacocks, undated, circa 1923; cuid5586 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Hand-tinted Image, Unidentified People, Pigs, undated, circa 1923; cuid5587 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Mounted Photographs with Notation: Shelter Island, Manhanset House, Ships, Unidentified People - Property of Andrew Fiske, undated, circa 1920s; 2005; cuid5588 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Garden, undated, circa 1920s; cuid5589 (Box 124, Folder 24)
      Separated Materials Note
      These materials were originally housed with and separated from the "Snapshot Book with Orange Flower on Cover."
    - Photograph: Sylvester Manor, undated, circa 1920s; cuid5590 (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Mounted Photograph: Wellesley College, Signed by Alice Elvira Freeman Palmer, 1884 Christmas; cuid5591 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Photographic Print: Interior, Spinning Wheel, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5592 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Photograph: Sylvester Manor Garden, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5593 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Gardens, Unidentified Woman & Dog, undated, circa 1900 - 1920; cuid5594 (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Photograph: Sylvester Manor Gardens, undated, circa 1900 - 1920s; cuid5595 (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Horseriding, Unidentified People, undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5596 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Photograph: Unidentified Cambridge Home, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5597 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Unidentified Inlet, Lakeside, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5598 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Unidentified Man, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5599 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Unidentified Homes, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5600 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Mounted Photograph: Trail Among Trees, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5601 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Mounted Photograph: Hand-tinted "Greek Cottage," Unidentified Woman, Chickens, Dog, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5602 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Mounted Photographs: Gardiners Island Grounds, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5603 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Mounted Photograph: Norumbega Monument at Stony Brook & Charles River, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5604 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Mounted Photographs, Envelope, Notation: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Horsford Family, Unidentified People, Peacock, undated, circa 1879 - 1923; cuid5605 (Box 125, Folder 10)
      These materials were separated from the archival folder collected for author Mac Griswold.
    - Photographic Book: Trip to Amsterdam, Bermuda, Paris, undated; cuid5606 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Sherwood Forest Manor, Charles City, VA by Andrew Fiske, 1939; cuid5607 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Photograph: Unidentified Grounds, undated; cuid5737
    - Tintype with Enclosure: Shelter Island Grounds, 1883 August; cuid5608 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Film Negatives: "Good Haying", undated; cuid5609 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Film Negatives: "Peacock walk and east fence", undated; cuid5610 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Film Negatives: "Fish Garden", undated; cuid5611 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Film Negatives with Photographs: “Cousin Annie’s Garden”, undated; cuid5612 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Film Negatives with Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Interiors, undated; cuid5613 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Film Negatives: Shelter Island WWI Monument, undated; cuid5614 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Film Negatives: "East Piazza in Rose Time", undated; cuid5615 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Film Negatives: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, undated; cuid5616 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Film Negatives: "Breakfast Table, Etc.", undated; cuid5617 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Film Negatives: "Gardiner Grave in New London & Cottage at Cutchogue", undated; cuid5618 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Film Negatives: "Harvest Festival", undated; cuid5619 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Film Negatives: "Garden, Lovely, Clear", undated; cuid5620 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Film Negatives: "All Peacock", 1817; cuid5621 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Film Negatives: "Best Garden", undated; cuid5622 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Film Negative: Garden Bench, 1916; cuid5623 (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Film Negative: "Barns from Old Road - Not Good," "Sunlight from St. Kitts", undated; cuid5624 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Film Negatives: Sylvester Manor Gardens, undated; cuid5625 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Film Negatives: [French Kodak Package], circa 1900; cuid5626 (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Film Negatives: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, undated; cuid5627 (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - Film Negatives: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, undated; cuid5628 (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Interiors, Unidentified Children, Men, Women, Cat, Dog, [Fiske Family Scrapbook Images], undated, circa 1880 - 1940s; cuid5629 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Bundle of Photographs with Notation: "Return to Mabel Tower," [Tightly Curled, Inaccessible], undated, circa 1880 - 1940s; cuid5630 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Series C: Research Images
    - Photographs with Envelope & Notation: "Prints of Unidentified Scandinavian Landscape" [Iceland Expedition], undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5631 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Photographs with Correspondence: Norumbega Research, Unidentified Landscape, circa 1896; cuid5632 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Photographs with Envelope: Norumbega Research, circa 1896; cuid5633 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Mounted Photographs, Drawings with Envelope: Erlingsson Expedition, Iceland, 1895; cuid5634 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Mounted Photographs: Archaeological Dig, undated, circa 1890 - 1920s; cuid5635 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Mounted Photograph: Still Life with Urn, Candle, Fruit, undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5636 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Mounted Photograph: Prints of Angels, undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5637 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Ships, SS Flandre, circa 1958; cuid5638 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Photograph: Statue, Andrew Fiske, 1991 May; cuid5639 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Photograph: Lion Gardiner Statue, undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5640 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Photograph, Drawing, Envelope: Waterfront Scene, Andrew Fiske, 1974; cuid5641 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Mounted Photograph of Painting: "Sylvester L'Hommedieu, Aged 22, From a Portrait by Sir Benjamin West", undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5642 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Photograph of a Drawing: Windmill, Andrew Fiske, undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5643 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Mounted Photocopy: Richard Nicolls Document, undated, circa 1940s - 1960s; cuid5644 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Mounted Photographs of Documents, Envelope: "War of 1812", undated, circa 1940 - 1960s; cuid5645 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Photographs of Documents, Envelope: 18th Century, undated, circa 1973; cuid5646 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Film Negatives of Correspondence: William Floyd to Ezra L'Hommedieu, [Original Date 1783], undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5647 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Film Negative of Correspondence: 19th Century, Andrew Fiske, undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5648 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Film Negatives of Correspondence: Ezra L'Hommedieu & George Clinton, undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5649 (Box 126, Folder 19)
      Please find Box 2, Folders 43-45 for the original Ezra L'Hommedieu and George Clinton correspondence.
    - Film Negatives of Correspondence: Joseph Henry to Eben Norton Horsford, [Orignal Date 1886], undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5650 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Film Negatives of Documents, Envelope: Andrew Fiske, [Original Date 1780-1783], 1955, undated; cuid5651 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Film Negatives of Document, Paintings: Windmill, Sylvester L''Hommedieu, undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5652 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Film Negative: Boats, Andrew Fiske, undated, circa 1950 - 1970s; cuid5653 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Series D: Albums
    - Photo Album: Fiske Family, 1913 - 1915; cuid5654 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Photo Album: Fiske Family, circa 1910 - 1918; cuid5655 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Photo Album: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Unidentified Children, undated; cuid5656 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Photo Album: Horsford Family, Sylvester Manor, undated; cuid5657 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Historical Structure Report Photo Album, undated; cuid5658 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Dark Green Kodak Photo Album, undated; cuid5659 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Photo Album: Unidentified People, Mary Gardiner Horsford Fiske, undated; cuid5660 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Sylvester Manor Scrapbook: Art, Documents, Photographs, undated, circa 1870s - 1910s; cuid5661 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Series E: Glass Plate Negatives and Slides
    - "No. N - Water Garden", undated; cuid5662 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - "No. K - Corner of Wood Road", undated; cuid5663 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - "No. 42 - Lilian and Sherman in the Golden Parrot", undated; cuid5664 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - "No. F - Lawn from Piazza", undated; cuid5665 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - "No. G - Poultry Yard Lane", undated; cuid5666 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - [Unlabeled Negative of Garden], undated; cuid5667 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - "No. J - Lower garden from poultry yard", undated; cuid5668 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - "No. O - Group by water garden", undated; cuid5669 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - "No. 35 - Dr. Storrs", undated; cuid5670 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - "No. 37 - Gog and Magog", undated; cuid5671 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - "No. 44 - View toward summer house", undated; cuid5672 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - [Unlabeled Negative of Garden], undated; cuid5673 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - "Kate by Balustrade", undated; cuid5674 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - "No. I - Birch Tree in the Woods", undated; cuid5675 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - "No. 36 - Slave Burying Ground", undated; cuid5676 (Box 137, Folder 15)
    - "No. U - Apple Tree and Hydrangeas", undated; cuid5677 (Box 137, Folder 16)
    - "No. 41 - Mack in Box Path", undated; cuid5678 (Box 137, Folder 17)
    - "No. 46 - Grass Path in Garden", undated; cuid5679 (Box 137, Folder 18)
    - "No. 43 - Lotus and Willow", undated; cuid5680 (Box 137, Folder 19)
    - "No. 33 - Lawn Facing Creek", undated; cuid5681 (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - "No. 34 - Fountain", undated; cuid5682 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - "No. 40 - Fountain", undated; cuid5683 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - "No. W - Mac in Water Garden", undated; cuid5684 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - "No. V - Manor House", undated; cuid5685 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - "No. T - Garden House and Steps", undated; cuid5686 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - "No. R - Piazza", undated; cuid5687 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - "No. Q - The Turn in the Wood Road Toward Woodstock", undated; cuid5688 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - [Unlabeled Negative of Water Garden], undated; cuid5689 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - "No. 45 - Big Willow and Gate", undated; cuid5690 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - "No. K - Terrace Steps with Lilies", undated; cuid5691 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - "No. M - House with Poplars", undated; cuid5692 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - "No. L - Manor Gate", undated; cuid5693 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Glass Negative Enclosure #2, [Glass Present, No Image], undated; cuid5694 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Glass Negative Enclosure #12, [Glass Present, No Image], undated; cuid5695 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Glass Plate Negative Envelopes, undated; cuid5696 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - [Woman In Front Of Fireplace], undated; cuid5697 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - "Mamma, Papa, Mamie & Gertrude", undated; cuid5698 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Color Glass Slide: [Woman at Monument], undated; cuid5699 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Color Glass Slide: [Garden Flowers], undated; cuid5700 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Glass Slide: [Garden Path], undated; cuid5701 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Glass Negative Envelope, undated; cuid5702 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Series F: Cornelia Horsford Nitrate Negatives
    - Unidentified Gardens, undated; cuid4676 (Box No Original)
    - Unidentified Gardens and Figures, undated; cuid4677 (Box No Original)
    - Unidentified Homes, undated; cuid4678 (Box No Original)
  - Photographic Material: Oversize
    - Oversize Series A: People and Portraits
      - Mounted Photographs in Enclosure: Portrait of Andrew Fiske; Gertrude Horsford Fiske with Grandchildren, circa 1917; cuid5703 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Mounted Photograph: Unidentified Girls in Garden, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5704 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Mounted Photograph in Enclosure: Unidentified Priest, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5705 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Photograph & Reproductions: Portrait of Ms. Sylvanus Reed, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5706 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Mounted Photograph: Portrait of Eben Norton Horsford, undated, circa 1880s; cuid5707 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Photograph with Engravings: Portrait of Eben Norton Horsford, undated, circa 1880s; cuid5708 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - Engravings: Portrait of Eben Norton Horsford, undated, circa 1880s; cuid5709 (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Mounted Photographic Prints: Painted Portraits of Andrew Fiske & Gertrude Horsford Fiske, 1920 January; 1930 July; cuid5710 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Mounted Photographs in Enclosure: Portraits, Unidentified Women, undated, circa 1917; cuid5711 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Mounted Photograph: Unidentified People at Sylvester Manor, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5712 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Photograph: Unidentified Woman & Child, 1907; cuid5713 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Mounted Photograph: Portrait of Mary Gardiner Horsford, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5714 (Box 152, Folder 26)
      - Mounted Photograph: Portrait of Phoebe Dayton Gardiner Horsford, undated, circa 1900s; cuid5715 (Box 152, Folder 27)
    - Oversize Series B: Sylvester Manor, 27 Craigie Street
      - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds by H.D. Bastow, [Fragile, Damaged], undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5716 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Mounted Photograph: Sylvester Manor Front Lawn by H.D. Bastow, undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5717 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens, Gardiners Island, undated, circa 1920 - 1940s; cuid5718 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Mounted Photograph: Albany Female Academy by Albion W. Floyd, undated, circa 1880 - 1900s; cuid5719 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Mounted Photographs with Notation: Sylvester Manor Grounds by Frances E. Johnston, undated, circa 1920 - 1960s; cuid5720 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Mounted Photograph: Quaker Burial Ground Memorial Dedication, undated, circa 1880 - 1920s; cuid5721 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens by H.D. Bastow & Frances B. Johnston, undated, circa 1920 - 1960s; cuid5722 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds, Gardens by H.D. Bastow & Frances B. Johnston, undated, circa 1920 - 1960s; cuid5723 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Mounted Photographs: Horse Carriage, Sylvester Manor by H.D. Bastow & 27 Craigie Street, undated, circa 1880 - 1940s; cuid5724 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Historic Structure Report Mounted Photographs: Sylvester Manor Grounds by H.D. Bastow, Unidentified Woman, undated, circa 1900 - 1940s; cuid5725 (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - Mounted Photographs: Henry W. Longfellow Research, undated; cuid5726 (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Photograph: Brook Point Harbor, 1870; cuid5727 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Photographs: Unidentified Church, undated; cuid5728 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Photographs: Unidentified House, undated; cuid5729 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Photographs: Railroad Scenes, Toltec Tunnel, undated; cuid5730 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Oversize Series C: Research Images
      - Photographs: "Reports, dig plans and photographs re: Icelandic expedition and archaeologic sites in Cambridge", circa 1896; cuid5731 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Photograph with Notation: Silver Plate, 1884; cuid5732 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Record Group VII: Artifacts
  Record Group VII: Artifacts includes original housing containers in the form of document boxes, letter files, trunks, and wallets. These containers once provided storage for the documents and photographs previously described in this collection.
  - Metal Lockbox, undated; cuid5733 (Box 156)
    This metal lockbox belonged to Andrew Fiske.
  - Metal Lockbox, undated; cuid5734 (Box 157)
    This metal lockbox includes letter satchels, small frames, a cigar box with ship records, and metal writing implements; the metal writing implements were originally housed with the materials from Box 107, Folder 25.
  - Assorted Containers, undated; cuid5735 (Box 158)
    This assortment includes empty boxes, file folders, and letter wallets that once housed correspondence and photographic negatives.
  - Oversize Boards, undated; cuid5736 (Box 159)
    These containers once housed engravings, large maps, and other oversize documents.